William Lee

Contact

Address:

Sai Kung, Hong Kong

Email:

williamlee19940628@gmail.com

Phone:

+86 13394438755

Proficient

- React.js | Vue.js
- Express.js | Laravel
- MongoDB | MySQL

Knowledgeable

- Angular.js | jQuery
- ASP.NET
- React Native
- MSSQL

Some experience

- Django | Flask
- Flutter
- Kotlin | Swift
- PostgreSQL

Languages

English

Summary

Innovative, creative, and a proven team player and 8 years experience of building, developing, and managing websites, applications and programs for various organizations. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks and personally picking up the slack when necessary. With a passion for both personal growth and for software development, I always look forward to learn new languages while sharpening existing skills. Interested in securing the position of Senior Web/Mobile Developer at talented engineering team, hoping to share great skills, expertise, and experience with company's team and valuable clients.

Experience

Full Stack Developer - 01/2021 to 09/2022

SnapFood, Albania (Remote)

Website, Android, iOS

- Developed website using React.js+Laravel
- Developed admin dashboard using Laravel+Admin LTE
- Developed mobile apps using React Native+Laravel
- Integrate firebase and payment apis (Paypal, Stripe, Apple pay)

Web Developer - 02/2018 to 11/2020

Sprocess Online, UK (Remote) Casir

<u>Casinopurple</u>, <u>Casinoeagles</u>

- Developed website using Vue.js+Express.js
- Integrate game apis from 70+ game studios (Evoplay, Gamzix, BetSoft, InBetGames etc)
- Integrate 50+ payment apis (Visa, CreditCard, Skrill, SecurionPay etc)

Freelancer - 04/2015 to 11/2017

- Developed restaurant app using Vue.js+Laravel (https://github.com/william0628/restaurant-app)
- Developed mobile app using React Native (https://github.com/william0628/syna-mobile)
- Developed sport betting website using Laravel (https://github.com/william0628/BettingFootball)
- Developed mobile app using Swift (https://github.com/william0628/fooddelivery)
- Developed CRUD app using MERN stack (https://github.com/william0628/MERN-crud-app)
- Developed dating website using HTML5+Django (https://github.com/william0628/dating-website)

Education

Bachelor's Degree in **Computer Science** 2012-2016 **Chinese University of Hong Kong** - Shatin, NT Hong Kong